rttnews.com 2019-06-20

# RTTNews - Privacy Policy

---  
RTTNews is committed to protecting your privacy. This statement of our Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from you and how we use that information as it relates to RTTNews' services, including ad placements, advertising, marketing and lead generation. We consider the information you have shared with us strictly confidential and will use that information only as specified in this Privacy Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law.   
  
### Information We Gather and How We Use It  
  
We collect certain information from you in order to provide you with the most interesting and useful Content possible. We use your IP address to identify you, to gather demographic information that helps us understand how you and our other customers use our Website, and to administer our Website. Our registration forms requires you to give us contact information (e.g. name and email address), demographic information (e.g. country). We use your contact information to contact you about our Website and provide you with information and promotional material from our partners and advertisers. From time to time we may supplement information that you provide to us with information received from third parties. 

Non-personally identifiable information is information that cannot be tracked to a specific individual. RTTNews may collect non-personally identifiable information while you are visiting the RTTNews Website or the Website of one of RTTNews advertisers. With each advertising impression served, RTTNews collects information such as the time of day, URL visited, browser type, browser language, and IP address. RTTNews analyzes certain web pages of those advertisers’ websites within our network. RTTNews may use page content, form data and URL parameters in order to improve its service to the users. RTTNews may place advertisements of third-party advertisers on its Websites.  If you choose to click on an advertisement, RTTNews may provide non-personally identifiable information to the advertiser. 

The advertisers may use the information collected from you to serve Interest-based advertising (IBA) which allow them to deliver targeted advertising. IBA usually works by displaying advertisements that are based on the type of content you access or read. You can make use of Network Advertising Initiative's (NAI) Opt Out Tool (<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>) to restrain yourself from receiving IBA. When you select this option, no information from you will be utilized for IBA and there will not be any customization relevant to you. However, it does not mean that you will never receive any advertisement from us for the period in which you are using our services.   
  
### How long we keep your information  
  
We retain personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill any legal obligations we may have as well as for purposes of processing your information (for example, if you continue to subscribe to one of our services, we will need your information to deliver the service to you).  We may also retain aggregate information beyond this time for research purposes and to help us develop and improve our services. You cannot be identified from aggregate information retained or used for these purposes.   
  
### Information We May Disclose  
  
We share demographic, profile and other general information about you and our other customers with our advertisers on an aggregate basis. This means that we tell our advertisers general information about the characteristics of our customer base (e.g. geographical).

Our advertisers may ask us to mail or e-mail you promotional information tailored to your interests. We will send you this information on behalf of our advertisers. From time to time we may use third parties (pursuant to a confidentiality agreement) to assist us in e-mail broadcasts and list management. You may opt-out of receiving these mailings as explained below under the heading "Your Rights/How to Contact Us."

We may release your contact and other information to third parties when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) cooperate with state and federal regulatory agency investigations, (iii) enforce the terms of our third party agreements, or (v) protect the rights of rttnews.com or others.   
  
### Cookies  
  
Our Website uses “cookies” which deposit certain record keeping information in your hard drive. A cookie is a file that the Internet browser places on your computer's hard drive. It is not a virus and cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer. A cookie controls the delivery rate of ads to Web browsers such that the number of times a Web browser receives any one advertisement is limited to ensure the best online experience for our users. A cookie also allows RTTNews reporting system to estimate the total reach of an ad campaign so that our advertisers can determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. When applicable we may use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, keep track of your preferences, deliver content specific to your interests, and for other similar purposes. These cookies can't read other data from your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites or applications.

Our Website contains display ads sold by us or by outside advertising agencies. These ads may contain cookies which will be deposited in your hard drive if you click on the ads. Information generated from cookies deposited on your hard drive by our advertisers is collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. 

Most browsers are set to accept cookies unless you reconfigure your browser to refuse them or to notify you when you have received one. If you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of our site. Although cookies enhance the online experience, Web users always have the option of blocking the use of the same by altering a setting in their browser. Please see your browser supplier's Website for details on how this may be done if you object to the collection of non-personally identifiable information.  
  
### Submission of Personally Identifiable Information  
  
When using services offered through RTTNews or its customers and affiliates, you may choose to enter your name, contact information, and other personal information. You will have clear notification that we are collecting this information so that you can choose not to provide it. Users may also provide contact information while visiting rttnews.com to request information.   
  
### Use of the Information We Collect  
  
#### Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
  
RTTNews may use non-personally identifiable information collected to improve the quality of RTTNews services, for example, by increasing ad placements on Websites that are receiving more Web traffic and presenting you with ads that we think you would be interested in viewing RTTNews may market its services by sharing Web surfing data with business partners in such a way that you are not identified. RTTNews also may provide your non-personally identifiable information to companies so that they can perform services for us.  
  
#### Use of Personally Identifiable Information  
  
RTTNews does not provide personally identifiable information to third parties except under the following conditions. If you provide personally identifiable information as part of an inquiry about products or services provided by one of our business partners, we will provide that information only to that business partner so that they may attempt to provide you with information regarding the products or services you inquired about. RTTNews may use the personally identifiable information provided by users or business partners at rttnews.com for internal purposes, such as sales, human resources, marketing, and administration (e.g., billing, newsletters and communicating with our business partners and maintaining their account information). We may share this information with third parties who provide RTTNews with administrative services. If RTTNews shares any of the information collected from you with a third party, their use of that information will be governed by the third party's privacy policy.  
  
#### Subscriptions and Purchases  
  
You may subscribe for a fee to certain services through our Website. Any financial information we collect will be used solely to bill you for the services and items you have purchased.   
  
### Security  
  
Our Web site has certain security measures in place in effort to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our Website contains links to other sites. RTTnews.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. You may wish to review the privacy policies of these sites.  
  
### Child Protection  
  
RTTNews does not offer services to, or target, persons under the age of 18. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we receive from people we believe to be minors will be purged from our database.   
  
### Acceptance of Privacy Statement  
  
Your use of our Website is subject to this privacy policy. **BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.** We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the effective date at the bottom of this page to determine if the privacy policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of our Website following posting of the updated privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.  
  
### Your Rights/How to Contact Us  
  
####  Opt out of receiving promotional materials from our advertisers or messages from [https://www.rttnews.com](https://www.rttnews.com/).   
  
You may opt-out during the registration process or after registering by visiting us at https://www.rttnews.com and using the contact us link to contact us. Every e-mail we send to you will provide you with instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future e-mails.   
  
#### Correct or Update Your Information  
  
You may correct or update any information previously provided to us by visiting us at [ https://www.rttnews.com ](https://www.rttnews.com/)and using the contact us link to contact us.  
  
####  European Users  
  
If you give us permission, we will send you news and promotional materials about our Services. You can change your mind about this at anytime and withdraw the consent and ask us not to process your Information for direct marketing purposes and promotions. 

RTTNews.com subscribers can have a copy of the information provided with us for a set period of the contract and can ask to correct, delete or to stop any active information. In addition, subscribers have the right to obtain the information provided with us in machine-readable format or to share this information with another controller. 

You have the right to raise the objection in the processing of the information, especially when we are not bound to process the information to abide by the legal or contractual requirement. There will be limited rights for the subscribers to request for revealing information about another person or to delete information that is to be preserved as per the law of the land or in a compelling legitimate interest. 

You have the right to withdraw the consent on information that you have given us for marketing or other purposes. You can specify if you are not interested in using your information for direct marketing purpose and also can opt out of emails, newsletters, or other marketing communications by choosing opt-out options provides in those emails. 

To exercise any of these rights, you can get in touch with us using our Contact Us page. Please include your registration Information such as first name, last name and e-mail address in the request. We may ask you to provide additional Information for identity verification purposes or to verify that you are in possession of an applicable email account.   
  
### Additional Information  
  
For general information about Internet privacy issues, you may wish to visit the Web site hosted by the Federal Trade Commission at <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy> . 

We may from time to time revise this Privacy Policy. This statement of our Privacy Policy was last revised on May 31, 2018.
